<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Web on Ceso Adventures</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/tags/web/</link><description>Recent content in Web on Ceso Adventures</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ceso.github.io/tags/web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hack The Box - Obscurity</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/obscurity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/obscurity/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://ceso.github.io/images/htb/obscurity/info-card.png" class="center" style="border-radius: 8px;" /&gt;


&lt;h2 id="quick-summary"&gt;Quick Summary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, the last months I have been really away from doing write-ups, specifically due to being full focused on my OSCP which I still can&amp;rsquo;t belive I passed!! I did an extensive write up about my experience going through it, if you still haven&amp;rsquo;t read it &lt;a href="https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/04/a-journey-in-the-dark-an-adventures-tale-towards-oscp/"&gt;you can click here to go to it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have more machines to do a write-up of, for example some of them are Postman, Traverxec, Mango, SolidState, OpenAdmin, Chatter Box among others, but well&amp;hellip;I will try to do them as my time allows me hehe.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Hack The Box - Bitlab</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/bitlab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/bitlab/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://ceso.github.io/images/htb/bitlab/info-card.png" class="center" style="border-radius: 8px;" /&gt;


&lt;h2 id="quick-summary"&gt;Quick Summary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First than everything, I need to make clear that this box has 2 ways for doing privilege escalation: one is doing reversing and the other taking advantage of a misconfiguration with sudo and git. I will describe the steps for the &lt;code&gt;sudo + git&lt;/code&gt; path as I&amp;rsquo;m just starting to do my first steps into more low-level stuff. Despite this, in the future I will actualize this post to reflect also the reversing path.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Hack The Box - Craft</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/craft/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/craft/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://ceso.github.io/images/htb/craft/info-card.png" class="center" style="border-radius: 8px;" /&gt;


&lt;h2 id="quick-summary"&gt;Quick Summary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So!!
Today was just retired Craft from Hack the box, this was a really fun box to do, and also I felt pretty well doing it, because even if I needed some nudges, it was actually the first box I got to the foothold without hints (elsen if I needed some guidance with python, thanks a lot @Frundrod!!), and afterward to get user I was a bit lost and also needed some hints (was not realizing something I have literally in my nose, thankss a lot &lt;a href="https://www.hackthebox.eu/profile/103596"&gt;@Fugl!&lt;/a&gt;), root was easy by a little bit of enumeration and reading help command output.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>