<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tryharder on Ceso Adventures</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/tags/tryharder/</link><description>Recent content in Tryharder on Ceso Adventures</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ceso.github.io/tags/tryharder/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wehmütig</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2025/wehmutig.de/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2025/wehmutig.de/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://ceso.github.io/images/blog/general/wehmutig.png" class="center" style="border-radius: 10x;" /&gt;


&lt;h1 id="wehmütig"&gt;Wehmütig&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wie der Donner, der dem vorbeiziehenden Blitz folgt, so umarmte sie mich - Verfinsterung&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Zerdenken</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2025/zerdenken.de/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2025/zerdenken.de/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://ceso.github.io/images/blog/general/zerdenken.png" class="center" style="border-radius: 10x;" /&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Als es April 2022 war, habe ich einen Post auf Schwedisch geschreiben, weil ich angefangen habe, Schwedisch zu lernen. Ich erinnere mich nicht, wann genau ich aufgehört habe, Schwedisch zu lernen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Im Februar 2023 bin ich nach Deutschland umgezogen. Als ich umgezogen bin, habe ich anfangen, um Deutsch zu lernen. Jetzt lerne ich seit ungefähr zwei Jahren Deutsch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Es ist ein bisschen komisch, aber ich habe das Gefühl, dass ich etwas auf Deutsch ausdrucken kann, was ich in meiner Muttersprache (Spanisch) nicht konnte - sogar wenn ich viele Fehler mache.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Hur jag är lär mig svenska</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2022/larmigsvenska.se/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2022/larmigsvenska.se/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://ceso.github.io/images/blog/general/larsvenska.png" class="center" style="border-radius: 8px;" /&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Förneka: Deta blogginlägget har mycket fel, jag vet det, men&amp;hellip;jag vill bara skriva lite om hur jag lär mig svenska, så det är en lite öva för mig, ingenting allvarlig!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vad kan säga jag? Jag gillar hur germanska språk ljud, och jag också gillar många metal-band från sverige (och svenska kultur), för det anledning beslutade jag lär mig svenska (i framtiden jag skulle vilja också lär tyska och holländska).&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Three is Company: My adventure getting OSEP towards landing OSCE3</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2022/threeiscompany/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2022/threeiscompany/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://ceso.github.io/images/blog/osep/osep_banner.png" class="center" style="border-radius: 8px;" /&gt;


&lt;h2 id="preface"&gt;Preface&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twenty months have passed since ceso obtained his OSCP and just now in January/2022 got his OSEP, during this time he traveled from the old continent back to his hometown on the other side of the world as there was stuff he needed to sort out. Covid-19 (c-19), the pandemic that started in 2020, was still leaving havoc behind any place where it arrived, and the situation didn&amp;rsquo;t look like getting better any soon. His travel back was not the easiest one as it used to be before the c-19 attacked but still, as it was he was able to return without facing odds.
Ceso saved some money and made ambitious objectives when it was still 2021; &amp;ldquo;I will get OSCE3!!!&amp;rdquo;, but&amp;hellip;stuff doesn&amp;rsquo;t always go as expected or how we want, and his life started to go downhill in some aspects of his life, health started to be quite
an issue and all his plans needed to be pushed aside and improving his health turned the top priority.
Months passed and as he started to feel better, August of 2021 was running and decided it was time, he was ready to continue where he left, time to pick up before all started going downhill; time to go after OSEP and defeat it and the bosses that will be coming afterward (OSWE and OSED).&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>