<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thoughts on Ceso Adventures</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/tags/thoughts/</link><description>Recent content in Thoughts on Ceso Adventures</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ceso.github.io/tags/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Three is Company: My adventure getting OSEP towards landing OSCE3</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2022/threeiscompany/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2022/threeiscompany/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://ceso.github.io/images/blog/osep/osep_banner.png" class="center" style="border-radius: 8px;" /&gt;


&lt;h2 id="preface"&gt;Preface&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twenty months have passed since ceso obtained his OSCP and just now in January/2022 got his OSEP, during this time he traveled from the old continent back to his hometown on the other side of the world as there was stuff he needed to sort out. Covid-19 (c-19), the pandemic that started in 2020, was still leaving havoc behind any place where it arrived, and the situation didn&amp;rsquo;t look like getting better any soon. His travel back was not the easiest one as it used to be before the c-19 attacked but still, as it was he was able to return without facing odds.
Ceso saved some money and made ambitious objectives when it was still 2021; &amp;ldquo;I will get OSCE3!!!&amp;rdquo;, but&amp;hellip;stuff doesn&amp;rsquo;t always go as expected or how we want, and his life started to go downhill in some aspects of his life, health started to be quite
an issue and all his plans needed to be pushed aside and improving his health turned the top priority.
Months passed and as he started to feel better, August of 2021 was running and decided it was time, he was ready to continue where he left, time to pick up before all started going downhill; time to go after OSEP and defeat it and the bosses that will be coming afterward (OSWE and OSED).&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Q3liZXJzZWMgbXkgd2F 5IC0gUGFydCAxCg==</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2021/cybersecmyway/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2021/cybersecmyway/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="preface"&gt;Preface&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lot of things have happend since the last time I posted something here, such as moving back to my country at the middle of last year to also stopping studying for some months due prioritizing my mental health (2020 was a bitch to all of us).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I already talked a bit about my background and how I started to study Cybersec in my prior post related to &lt;a href="https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/04/a-journey-in-the-dark-an-adventures-tale-towards-oscp/"&gt;my experience with OSCP&lt;/a&gt;, you can go there and read about it if you want, but I will repeat some stuff here.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>A Journey in the Dark - An adventure's tale towards OSCP</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/ajourneyinthedark/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/ajourneyinthedark/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://ceso.github.io/images/blog/oscp/oscp_banner.png" class="center" style="border-radius: 8px;" /&gt;


&lt;h2 id="preface"&gt;Preface&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the story of how I got my OSCP coming from a background as Linux Sysadmin/DevOps as also which ones are my plans for the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every tale where there is an adventurer, starts with him (the adventurer) and his friends, these who share the journey providing support and advice through it, as the story moves forward, new characters tend to appear, joining the adventurer in his travel.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>shutdown -r now</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2019/shutdown-r-now/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2019/shutdown-r-now/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Note: First than everything, sorry the english, is not my native language and always learning new stuff about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have always been thinking about writing a blog, but my mindset has always been the same &amp;ldquo;me? a blog? what am I supposed to post! I can&amp;rsquo;t even think anything I could share with people, I don&amp;rsquo;t know nothing compared to the people
who blogs!&amp;rdquo;, currently that mindset has been changing. In the same way, maybe I read a really entry-level article and at some moment and it was (or is) helpful for me, it also could be helpful for another person as well things faced, the issues I ran into, etc&amp;hellip;, and being some sort of way of escape for me itself, I think this change of mindset is the result of my last 9 months living abroad.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>