<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Infosec on Ceso Adventures</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/tags/infosec/</link><description>Recent content in Infosec on Ceso Adventures</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ceso.github.io/tags/infosec/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Three is Company: My adventure getting OSEP towards landing OSCE3</title><link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2022/threeiscompany/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2022/threeiscompany/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://ceso.github.io/images/blog/osep/osep_banner.png" class="center" style="border-radius: 8px;" /&gt;


&lt;h2 id="preface"&gt;Preface&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twenty months have passed since ceso obtained his OSCP and just now in January/2022 got his OSEP, during this time he traveled from the old continent back to his hometown on the other side of the world as there was stuff he needed to sort out. Covid-19 (c-19), the pandemic that started in 2020, was still leaving havoc behind any place where it arrived, and the situation didn&amp;rsquo;t look like getting better any soon. His travel back was not the easiest one as it used to be before the c-19 attacked but still, as it was he was able to return without facing odds.
Ceso saved some money and made ambitious objectives when it was still 2021; &amp;ldquo;I will get OSCE3!!!&amp;rdquo;, but&amp;hellip;stuff doesn&amp;rsquo;t always go as expected or how we want, and his life started to go downhill in some aspects of his life, health started to be quite
an issue and all his plans needed to be pushed aside and improving his health turned the top priority.
Months passed and as he started to feel better, August of 2021 was running and decided it was time, he was ready to continue where he left, time to pick up before all started going downhill; time to go after OSEP and defeat it and the bosses that will be coming afterward (OSWE and OSED).&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>